<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
  <ModMetaData>
	<name>Otter Pirates</name>
	<author>Ottersholdhands</author>
    <packageId>Ottersholdhands.Otter</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
	<url>https://i.imgur.com/UdyR1nx.png</url>
	<description>
The troubled tale of the Otter Pirates is a mystery shrouded under a bed of seaweed. Some say they were otters that evolved over eons to become sentient. Another says they were spacefarers with a stricken ship, crash-landed in the ocean's depths. Yet deep within the fishy underbelly of ports all over the rimworld, a different story is told. A story of a ship adrift, laden with advanced technologies beyond your wildest of dreams. Of a group of otters who aided a band of starving sailors and made an uncommon alliance. This story says that these otters helped a ship full of stranded sailors, gifting them food, water, and materials to repair their ship. Out of their acts of kindness, the flame of kinship was struck, and the Sailors taught them the way of the pirate. How to pillage, plunder and pilfer the richest hordes of fish and shiny coral. Their minds filled with the idea of endless fish and cities buried in shiny coral. Now, these otter pirates roam the coastline in an ever-growing fleet trading and raiding wherever they may land. Merchants and coastal towns say that the otters are ruthless traders, but often amicable to those who ply a fair deal. But never make the mistake of stealing their fish, many who never make it out alive.
Art Made By - @blackBerryTea2
Coded by - Ottersholdhands
Special thanks to Syrchalis, Kompad, Argentum, Laharl,  Kasmex for weapon art, Si-Cafe Fishing-ReWork Textures

  </description>
  <modDependencies>
   <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
   </li>
</modDependencies>
<loadBefore>
</loadBefore>
<loadAfter>
<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
</loadAfter>
  </ModMetaData>